thomasgriffin.io 2015-03-19

# Privacy - Thomas Griffin

I respect your privacy. The information I collect from you (name, email address) will be used to send you regular content updates, other promotional materials and possibly updates and/or promotions to other products and services that I build. It won’t be sold out to any 3rd party vendors.

Privacy is very important to me. Accordingly, I have developed these bullet points in order for you to understand how I collect, use, communicate and disclose and make use of your personal information.

  * Before or at the time of collecting personal information, I will identify the purposes for which information is being collected.
  * I will collect and use of personal information solely with the objective of fulfilling those purposes specified by me and for other compatible purposes, unless I obtain the consent of the individual concerned or as required by law.
  * I will only retain personal information as long as necessary for the fulfillment of those purposes.
  * I will collect personal information by lawful and fair means and, where appropriate, with the knowledge or consent of the individual concerned.
  * Personal data should be relevant to the purposes for which it is to be used, and, to the extent necessary for those purposes, should be accurate, complete, and up-to-date.
  * I will protect personal information by reasonable security safeguards against loss or theft, as well as unauthorized access, disclosure, copying, use or modification.
  * I will make readily available to customers information about my policies and practices relating to the management of personal information.
